{
    "subject": "resource/Hans_Schweikart",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Berlin",
    "human_readable": "Hans Schweikart was born in Berlin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9165149927139282,
            "question": "Were there any notable events happening in Berlin around the time of Hans Schweikart's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8892003893852234,
            "question": "Where was Hans Schweikart born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8130097985267639,
            "question": "What year was Hans Schweikart born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.725779116153717,
            "question": "What kind of life did Hans Schweikart likely lead growing up in Berlin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6192960143089294,
            "question": "What city is associated with Hans Schweikart's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5689672231674194,
            "question": "Are there any famous people who were also born in Berlin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40323007106781006,
            "question": "How might Hans Schweikart's birthplace have influenced his experiences and perspectives?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34760332107543945,
            "question": "Do you know any other facts about Hans Schweikart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2982909381389618,
            "question": "Is Hans Schweikart known for anything specific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15123136341571808,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Berlin?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hans Schweikart was born in Berlin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8549_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Hans Schweikart known for anything specific?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8549_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know any other facts about Hans Schweikart?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8549_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might Hans Schweikart's birthplace have influenced his experiences and perspectives?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8549_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8549_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8549_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8549_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8549_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8549_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8549_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8549_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8549_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8549_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8549_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple, as there are multiple mentions of Hans Schweikart's birthplace being Berlin."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently state that Hans Schweikart was born on October 1, 1895, in Berlin, Germany. Therefore, the statement \"Hans Schweikart was born in Berlin\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}